A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Speech Files, RG 5 FA434
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Speech Files, 1941-2004; 5; 38 document box(es)
  - 1963
    - C. Walter Nichols Award, New York University Graduate School of Business Administration, 1963 June 3 (Box 4, Folder 102)
      LSR's remarks upon being presented with C. Walter Nichols Award.
    - Izaak Walton League Dinner, Honorary Presidency, 1963 June 14 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - New York Hilton Hotel Opening, Rockefeller Center, 1963 June 26 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Breezy Point Park Proposals, New York City Parks, 1963 July 23 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Robert Moses State Park Dedication, State Council of Parks, 1963 September 17 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Parks for America Conference, 1963 September 26 (Box 5, Folder 107)
      65th Annual Conference of the American Institute of Park Executives, the American Association of Zoological Parks and Aquariums, and the National Conference on State Parks.
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology Corporation Meeting, Conservation and Outdoor Recreation, 1963 October 7 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - New York Botanical Gardens Advisory Council, 1963 October 17 (Box 5, Folder 109)
      LSR remarks entitled "Conservation and Outdoor Recreation"
    - Theodore Roosevelt Association, Presentation of Roosevelt Medal, 1963 October 27 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - American Forestry Association Dinner, Presentation of Distinguished Service Award, 1963 October 29 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Brooklyn YWCA (Young Women's Christian Association) 75th Anniversary Dinner, 1963 October 30 (Box 5, Folder 112)
      LSR's speech entitled "The Challenge of Responsibility - Today and Tomorrow."
    - Capital Budget Hearing, State Council of Parks Statement, 1963 November 14 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Rockefeller Center, Tree Lighting Ceremony, 1963 December (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - 1964
    - Alfred P. Sloan Awards in Cancer Research, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - State Council of Parks Meeting, 1964 January 15 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Little Dix Bay Dedication, Virgin Gorda, British Virgin Islands, Rockresorts, 1964 January 18 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - George Washington University, Honorary Degree (Doctor of Public Service), 1964 February 22 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Dedication of Kettering Laboratory, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1964 May 6 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - 75th Anniversary Fund Dinner, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1964 May 19 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Dedication of Norman Winston House, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1964 June 10 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Saratoga Performing Arts Center Groundbreaking Ceremony, 1964 June 30 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - National YWCA (Young Women's Christian Association) Conference on Outdoor Recreation and Conservation, 1964 July 5 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Beaver Island State Park Golf Course Dedication, State Council of Parks, 1964 July 30 (Box 6, Folder 124)
      LSR's remarks delivered by Conrad L. Wirth.
    - State Council of Parks, Report on Federal Legislation, 1964 August 24 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - 44th Annual Meeting, National Conference on State Parks, 1964 September 23 (Box 6, Folder 126)
      Title of speech: "The New Horizons for Conservation and Outdoor Recreation." Additional copies of speech in Folder 127.
    - 44th Annual Meeting, National Conference on State Parks, 1964 September 23 (Box 6, Folder 127)
      Title of speech: "The New Horizons for Conservation and Outdoor Recreation." Folder contains additional copies of speech. See also Folder 126.
    - State Council of Parks, Federal Report, 1964 October 8 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - YWCA (Young Women's Christian Association) National Board Meeting, Report on Conference on Outdoor Recreation and Conservation, 1964 October 28 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Squibb-Olin Senior Fellowship Luncheon, Olin Mathiesen Charitable Trust, 1964 November 10 (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - Capital Budget Hearing, Conservation and Parks, 1964 November 19 (Box 6, Folder 131)
      LSR speaking as Chairman of State Council of Parks.
    - Fort Lee Historical Park Commemoration, 1964 November 21 (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges, Second Institute on Administration, 1964 December 6 (Box 6, Folder 133)
      Title of speech: "That the Parts May Truly Make a Whole: A Layman's View."
  - 1965
    - Statement on Re-Election as Chairman, State Council of Parks, 1965 January 8 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Conservation Award, Rod and Gun Editors Association of Metropolitan New York, 1965 February 25 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Consolidated Edision Plant at Storm King Mountain, Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1965 March 9 (Box 7, Folder 136)
      LSR statement regarding Federal Power Commission decision to build Consolidated Edison Plant at Storm King Mountain.
    - Tocks Island National Recreation Area, House of Representatives Bill H.R. 89, 1965 April 27 (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Dedication of Howard Laboratory, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1965 May 7 (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - National Press Club, Remarks on Natural Beauty, 1965 May 21 (Box 7, Folder 139)
      Remarks to Press Club prior to White House Conference on Natural Beauty. See also Box 7, Folders 140 and 141.
    - The White House Conference on Natural Beauty, Opening Session, 1965 May 24 (Box 7, Folder 140)
      See also Box 7, Folders 139 and 141.
    - The White House Conference on Natural Beauty, Report to the President, 1965 May 25 (Box 7, Folder 141)
      See also Box 7, Folders 139 and 140.
    - Twenty and Thirty Year Club, Rockefeller Center, 1965 June 7 (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - Rockland Lake Opening, Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1965 June 15 (Box 7, Folder 143)
    - Fort Hamilton Parkway Playground Opening Ceremony, 1965 June 23 (Box 7, Folder 144)
      Ceremony marking the transfer of the Playground from the Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority to the Park Department of the City of New York.
    - Dedication of Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, Rockresorts, 1965 July 24 (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - National Council of State Garden Clubs and American Forestry Association Meeting, Opening Remarks, 1965 September 3 (Box 7, Folder 146)
      See also Box 7, Folder 147.
    - National Council of State Garden Clubs and American Forestry Association Banquet, Introduction of First Lady "Lady Bird" Johnson, 1965 September 7 (Box 7, Folder 147)
      See also Box 7, Folder 146.
    - Transfer of Title of Iona Island, Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1965 September 16 (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - Eastern Caribbean Conservation Conference, Governor's Reception, 1965 October 3 (Box 7, Folder 148A)
    - Visit of Princess Margaret and Lord Snowdon, Rockefeller Center, 1965 November 22 (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - 70th Annual Congress of American Industry, National Association of Manufacturers, 1965 December 2 (Box 7, Folder 150)
      LSR's remarks entitled "Business and Beauty."
    - National Newcomen Dinner Honoring Eastern Air Lines, Inc., The Newcomen Society in North America, 1965 December 2 (Box 7, Folder 151)
      Guest of honor, Floyd D. Hall, President and Chief Executive Officer of Eastern Air Lines, Inc.
    - National Recreation and Park Association, Trustees Meeting, 1965 December 4 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - 1966
    - State Council of Parks, Statement on Re-Election as Chairman, 1966 January 10 (Box 8, Folder 153)
    - Senate Committee on Commerce, Statement on S. 2507 and S. 2508, 1966 April 28 (Box 8, Folder 154)
    - President's Council on Recreation and Natural Beauty, Citizens Advisory Committee, Statement on Announcement, 1966 May 4 (Box 8, Folder 155)
    - Watts Branch Park, Washington, D.C., Opening, 1966 May 18 (Box 8, Folder 156)
    - National Recreation and Park Association, Trustees Meeting, 1966 May 21 (Box 8, Folder 157)
    - New Jersey Governor's Conference on Natural Beauty, 1966 June 1 (Box 8, Folder 158)
    - Twenty and Thirty Year Club, Rockefeller Center, 1966 June 6 (Box 8, Folder 159)
    - Gold Medal Presentation to Dr. Fairfield Osborn, New York Zoological Society, 1966 June 15 (Box 8, Folder 160)
    - Opening of Saratoga Performing Arts Center, 1966 July 9 (Box 8, Folder 161)
    - The Congress for Recreation and Parks, National Recreation and Park Association, 1966 October (Box 8, Folder 162)
      LSR speeches: Keynote address entitled "A Force for Good Cities," delivered October 10, 1966; Introduction of President Lyndon B. Johnson and Secretary of Commerce John T. Connor, delivered October 13, 1966.
    - Business and Professional Men's Association of Far Northeast, Award, 1966 October 27 (Box 8, Folder 163)
    - Texas Technological College, Honorary Doctor of Humanities Degree, 1966 November 1 (Box 8, Folder 164)
    - Keep America Beautiful, Inc., Special Award, 1966 November 10 (Box 8, Folder 165)
    - Association of Edison Illuminating Companies, Annual Meeting, 1966 November 30 (Box 8, Folder 166)
      LSR address entitled "The Role of the Utility Industry in the Quality of Our Environment."
    - St. Thomas Chamber of Commerce, Acceptance of Plaque, 1966 December 3 (Box 8, Folder 167)
    - Dedication of Russell A. Firestone Radiation Therapy Center, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1966 December 7 (Box 8, Folder 168)
    - National Industrial Conference Board, Inc., Conference on "Preserving Our Environment: Management of Pollution", 1966 December 15 (Box 8, Folder 169)
  - 1967
    - National Industrial Conference Board, Harry Rand Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 170)
    - Presentation of Gift to Alfonso Valdes, Dorado Beach Golf and Tennis Club, Rockresorts, 1967 January 14 (Box 9, Folder 171)
    - The Camp Fire Club of America, Acceptance of Medal of Honor, 1967January 19 (Box 9, Folder 172)
    - Hilo-Mainland Temporary Air Service, County of Hawaii, Rockresorts, 1967 January 26 (Box 9, Folder 173)
    - Natural Beauty and Recreation Congress, National Association of Counties, 1967 January 28 (Box 9, Folder 174)
      LSR speaking as Chairman of the President's Committee on Recreation and Natural Beauty
    - Dedication of "The Birds" Sculpture, Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, Rockresorts, 1967 January 29 (Box 9, Folder 175)
      Sculpture by Bumpei Akaji; given as gift to Laurance and Mary Rockefeller
    - White House Reception Honoring Citizens Advisory Committee on Recreation and Natural Beauty, 1967 February 18 (Box 9, Folder 176)
    - Governor's Second Annual Conference on Beautification and Planning, 1967 March 1 (Box 9, Folder 177)
    - "A Conservationist Speaks His Mind on Environment", 1967 March 20 (Box 9, Folder 178)
      Reprinted from March 20, 1967, issue of "Electrical World."
    - Acceptance of Frances K. Hutchinson Medal, Garden Clubs of America Annual Banquet, 1967 March 31 (Box 9, Folder 179)
    - Statement on New Park Legislation, State Council of Parks Meeting, 1967 April 10 (Box 9, Folder 180)
    - International Congress on the Spiritual Values of Tourism, 1967 April 16 (Box 9, Folder 181)
    - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital, White House Luncheon, 1967 April 27 (Box 9, Folder 182)
      Luncheon given by Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson.
    - Salesman of the Year Award, Sales and Marketing Executives of Hilo, 1967 May 31 (Box 9, Folder 183)
    - Dedication of George Perkins Marsh Home as National Historic Landmark, Woodstock Foundation, 1967 June 11 (Box 9, Folder 184)
    - American Association of Nurserymen, Inc., Awards Program, 1967 October 18 (Box 9, Folder 185)
    - Chicago Club Speech to Businessmen, in Conjunction with Task Force on Electric Utilities, 1967 October 18 (Box 9, Folder 186)
    - Designation of Lyndhurst as Historic Landmark, New York State Historic Trust, 1967 October 24 (Box 9, Folder 187)
    - Agriculture Yearbook Publication Ceremony, "Outdoors USA", 1967 October 25 (Box 9, Folder 188)
      Speech prepared but not delivered - delayed arrival.
    - Adirondack Mountain Club, 1967 October 28 (Box 9, Folder 189)
      LSR address entitled "The Adirondacks and the Future."
    - State Council of Parks and Outdoor Recreation, Budget Hearing, 1967 November 3 (Box 9, Folder 190)
    - Acceptance of Gold Medal Award, National Institute of Social Sciences, 1967 November 28 (Box 9, Folder 191)
    - National Recreation and Park Association Congress, 1967 December 4 (Box 9, Folder 192)
  - 1968
    General note
    Box 10, Folder 206, also contains information for the calendar year 1969.
    - New York Zoological Society Annual Members Meeting, 1968 January 9-10 (Box 9, Folder 193)
    - Class of 1932 Dinner, Princeton University, 1968 March 5 (Box 9, Folder 194)
      LSR remarks entitled "Princeton and Co-Education."
    - Presentation of "Community Action for Natural Beauty" (First Copy) to Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson; Comment on Appointment of Vice President Hubert H. Humphrey as Chairman of the President's Council on Recreation and Natural Beauty, White House, 1968 March 29 (Box 9, Folder 195)
    - Building Completion Fund Meeting, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1968 April 24 (Box 9, Folder 196)
    - Hudson River Tour, Visit of Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson, 1968 May 17 (Box 9, Folder 197)
      LSR introductions of Mayor John Lindsay, Mr. George Hartzog, and Mr. Fred Smith.
    - Society Annual Meeting, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1968 May 22 (Box 9, Folder 198)
      LSR speech entitled "The Third Era - A Re-dedication."
    - Joint Meeting of President's Council and Citizens' Advisory Committee on Recreation and Natural Beauty, 1968 June 21 (Box 9, Folder 199)
    - Acceptance of Honorary Membership, American Society of Landscape Architects 68th Annual Meeting, 1968 June 24 (Box 9, Folder 200)
      LSR address entitled "The Quality of Our Environment - The Challenge to Landscape Architects."
    - Joint House-Senate Colloquium on Environmental Policy, 1968 July 17 (Box 9, Folder 201)
    - Opening of New Wing, Mauna Kea Beach Hotel, Rockresorts, 1968 September 21 (Box 9, Folder 202)
    - Palmer Square Tree Planting, Princeton University, 1968 September 27 (Box 9, Folder 203)
      "Dedication of funds which would have otherwise been used for signs and billboads to the beautification of the town"; political candidates Foster Jacobs and Michael Erdman.
    - Receiving of Honorary Doctor of Laws Degree, University of Vermont, 1968 October 4 (Box 9, Folder 204)
    - Professional Staff Dinner, Presentation of Medallion to Reginald G. Coombe, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1968 October 9 (Box 10, Folder 205)
    - National Recreation and Park Association Presentation of Citation to Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson, White House, 1968 November 12, 1969 January (Box 10, Folder 206)
      File also includes message from LSR for inclusion in book presented to President Lyndon B. Johnson, January 1969.
  - 1969
    Box 10, Folder 206, listed under "1968", also contains information regarding an event in 1969.
    - Presentation of the Gold Medal to Dr. Harold J. Coolidge, New York Zoological Society Annual Meeting, 1969 January 8-9 (Box 10, Folder 207)
    - Plaza Hotel Dinner Honoring President and Mrs. Lyndon B. Johnson, 1969 January 13 (Box 10, Folder 208)
      Folder contains only cover sheet with date and occasion noted. No comments/speech/tribute in folder.
    - Joint Legislative Fiscal Committee Review, Budget 1969-70, New York State Capitol, 1969 February 28 (Box 10, Folder 209)
    - Appeal for Upgrading Regional Managers, Civil Service Commission, 1969 April 8 (Box 10, Folder 210)
      Appeal for reclassification of seven key management positions from the title and grade of regional manager, Grade 29, to the title and grade of regional director of parks and outdoor recreation, Grade 32.
    - Memorial Service for Eugene W. Kettering, Eulogy, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1969 April 21 (Box 10, Folder 211)
    - Huttleston Annual Award Presentations, State Council of Parks Meeting, 1969 May 12 (Box 10, Folder 212)
      Leonard L. Huttleston Executive Award to A. K. Morgan; Leonard L. Huttleston Staff Award to Roger H. Gingrich.
    - Philipsburg Manor, Opening, 1969 May 21 (Box 10, Folder 213)
    - Acceptance of Alfred P. Sloan, Jr. Memorial Award, American Cancer Society, 1969 June 4 (Box 10, Folder 214)
    - Dedication of Outpatient Building, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1969 September 16 (Box 10, Folder 215)
      Speech entitled "The Role of Memorial in Today's Society."
    - Fifth Avenue Association Award Presentation to Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1969 October 23 (Box 10, Folder 216)
    - Report to the President and the Environmental Quality Council, Citizens' Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality, 1969 November 20 (Box 10, Folder 217)
    - Dedication of Woodstock Inn, Vermont, Rockresorts, 1969 November 23 (Box 10, Folder 218)
    - Harlem River Park Project, Urban Development Corporation, 1969 December 8 (Box 10, Folder 219)
  - 1970
    Box 10, Folder 226, also contains information from the calendar year 1973.
    - The President's Report, New York Zoological Society, 1970 February 3 (Box 10, Folder 220)
    - Sea Star, Launching and Christening, 1970 March 23 (Box 10, Folder 221)
    - Earth Day Teach-In, Princeton University, 1970 April 21-22 (Box 10, Folder 222)
    - Acceptance of Building Fund Contribution, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1970 May 20 (Box 10, Folder 223)
      LSR remarks on accepting contribution from the Memorial Society for the Building Fund.
    - Dedication of Hudson Highlands State Park, State Council of Parks and Outdoor Recreation, 1970 May 23 (Box 10, Folder 224)
    - Outdoor Recreationist of the Year Award to Laurance S. Rockefeller, New York State Conservation Council, 1970 September 25 (Box 10, Folder 225)
    - State Dinner Honoring Laurance S. Rockefeller; State Dinner Honoring Mrs. W. Vincent (Brooke) Astor, Lotus Club, 1970 November 18; 1973 November 15 (Box 10, Folder 226)
    - Report to the Trustees, Highlights of the Past Year, New York Zoological Society, 1970 December 10 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - 1971
    - New York Zoological Society Annual Meeting, 1971 January 19 (Box 10, Folder 228)
    - Statement to National Industrial Pollution Control Council, 1971 February 10 (Box 10, Folder 229)
      LSR speaking as Chairman, Citizens' Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality.
    - Dinner Remarks Preceding the First Fairfield Osborn Memorial Lecture, Rockefeller University, 1971 March 23 (Box 10, Folder 230)
      Lecture series by New York Zoological Society, The Conservation Foundation, and The Rockefeller University.
    - "World of Birds" Party Given by Mrs. Lila Wallace, New York Zoological Society, 1971 April 2 (Box 10, Folder 231)
    - Group Affiliates Citations Night, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1971 April 21 (Box 10, Folder 232)
    - Richard D. Vanderwarker Memorial Service, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1971 May 12 (Box 11, Folder 233)
    - Dedication of A. K. Morgan Overlook Lodge, Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1971 May 17 (Box 11, Folder 234)
    - Society Annual Meeting, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1971 May 19 (Box 11, Folder 235)
    - Memorial Service for Dr. Connie Guion, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1971 May 25 (Box 11, Folder 236)
    - Alumni College Program, Princeton University, 1971 June 7 (Box 11, Folder 237)
      LSR address entitled: "The Environmental Movement -- Where Does It Go From Here?"
    - Alfred P. Sloan, Jr., Memorial Award Presentation to Mrs. Albert D. Lasker, American Cancer Society, 1971 June 9 (Box 11, Folder 238)
      LSR remarks as Dinner Chairman.
    - Advisory Council, Philosophy Department, Princeton University, 1971 September 17 (Box 11, Folder 239)
      Excerpts from "Take Off From Within" by Ervin Seale for LSR talk.
    - Dedication of Three National Recreation Trails, Palisades Interstate Park System, 1971 September 28 (Box 11, Folder 240)
    - Greenacre Park Opening, 1971 October 14 (Box 11, Folder 241)
      Remarks by LSR and Mrs. Jean (Babs) Mauzé.
    - Acceptance of National Award, American Cancer Society, 1971 November 5 (Box 11, Folder 242)
    - Statewide Parks Advisory Committee, 1971 November 15 (Box 11, Folder 243)
    - Second Annual Bear Mountain Christmas Festival, Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1971 December 10 (Box 11, Folder 244)
  - 1972
    - Acceptance of Charles Evans Hughes Award, Riverside Church, 1972 April 17 (Box 11, Folder 245)
    - Dedication of Colter Bay Indian Arts Museum, Grand Teton National Park, 1972 June 29 (Box 11, Folder 246)
      Collection owned by, and Museum built with assistance of, Jackson Hole Preserve, Incorporated.
    - Tenth Reunion, Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commission, 1972 July 26 (Box 11, Folder 247)
    - Dedication of The John D. Rockefeller Jr. Memorial Parkway, Grand Teton National Park, 1972 September 18 (Box 11, Folder 248)
      Jackson Hole Preserve, Inc.
    - Kawaihae Village Dedication, Puukohola National Historic Site Dedication, Rockresorts, 1972 November 4 (Box 11, Folder 249)
    - Trustees Meeting, Resignation of David Hunter McAlpin, New York Zoological Society, 1972 December 5 (Box 11, Folder 250)
    - Alfred Jacobsen Outpatient Building, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1972 December 19 (Box 11, Folder 251)
      Renaming of outpatient facility in Alfred Jacobsen's honor.
  - 1973
    Box 10, Folder 226, listed under "1970", also contains information from the calendar year 1973.
    - Four Hundred Third Meeting, Resignation as Chairman, State Council of Parks and Recreation, 1973 January 29 (Box 11, Folder 252)
    - L. L. Huttleston Executive Award, Presentation to Joseph Williams, Palisades Interstate Park Commission, 1973 May 14 (Box 11, Folder 253)
    - Task Force on Land Use and Urban Growth, Conference on Task Force Report, Citizens' Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality, 1973 May 24 (Box 11, Folder 254)
    - Alfred P. Sloan Jr., Memorial Award Presentation to Mr. Elmer Bobst, American Cancer Society, 1973 June 5 (Box 11, Folder 255)
    - Dedication of New Hospital, Staff and Public Ceremonies, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1973 November 13 and 14 (Box 12, Folder 256)
    - Introduction of Mrs. Brooke Astor, Lotus Club State Dinner, 1973 November 15 (Box 12, Folder 257)
    - Dedication of Spelman Halls, Princeton University, 1973 November 17 (Box 12, Folder 258)
    - "The Rockefellers," CBS Reports with Television News Correspondent Walter Cronkite, 1973 December 28 (Box 12, Folder 259)
  - 1974
    - Presentation of Vera Award to Jane Goodall, New York Zoological Society, 1974 April 30 (Box 12, Folder 260)
    - Welcome and Presentation of Volunteer Club Awards, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1974 May 14 (Box 12, Folder 261)
    - Acceptance of Dodge Medallion Award, YMCA, 1974 June 5 (Box 12, Folder 262)
      Award presented jointly to Mary and Laurance Rockefeller.
    - Luncheon Honoring Dr. Frank E. Adair, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1974 June 26 (Box 12, Folder 263)
    - Fund Raising Reception and Dinner, Lyndon Baines Johnson Memorial Grove, 1974 September 6 and 7 (Box 12, Folder 264)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Dinner Honoring Robert Moses and Laurance Rockefeller, State Council of Parks and Recreation, 1974 September 22 (Box 12, Folder 265)
    - Ground Breaking Ceremony, Lyndon Baines Johnson Memorial Grove, 1974 September 27 (Box 12, Folder 266)
    - Fund Raising Luncheon, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1974 November 7 (Box 12, Folder 267)
    - Twenty Year Club First Annual Dinner, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1974 November 12 (Box 12, Folder 268)
    - Statement Regarding Nelson Rockefeller's Nomination as Vice President, Senate Committee on Rules and Administration, 1974 November 15 (Box 12, Folder 269)